Casey Spaulding

Full-Stack .NET Software Developer

Address Davenport, FL, 33896

E-mail casey.spaulding@outlook.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/caseyspaulding/ **WWW** https://www.CaseySpaulding.com

Software Developer with training and experience in .NET, Bootstrap, HTML5, and Javascript programming. Bright critical thinker with proven talent for learning quickly in results-oriented environment. Supports team administrative, project coordination, design and programming needs. School projects included building apps, optimizing programs and validating code.

Certifications

2019-07 Security Clearance

Education

20211 - Current Bachelor of Science: Software Development

Western Governors University - Salt Lake City, UT

2007-08 - 20102 Bachelor of Science: Business Management

Marylhurst University - Marylhurst, OR

Work History

2019-08 - 2021-04 Teacher (Naval Science)

San Diego Unified School District, San Diego, CA

Teaches and mentors High School students with a curriculum emphasizing Naval Science.

- Scheduled and taught in class and online courses to increase learning opportunities.
- Planned and implemented integrated lessons to meet national standards.
- Devised and implemented strategies to create and maintain cohesive school community within virtual classroom setting.

Reference

Ron Flaherty

Teacher, San Diego Unified School District

2016-11 - 2019-08

Trainer

United States Navy, NRD San Diego, San Diego, CA

Responsible for the execution of Navy Recruiting District San Diego's training program. Provided command training to all hands, maintained command training files and tracking systems, and ensured compliance with applicable instructions and policies.

- Recorded and edited videos for use in later courses or by remote learners.
- Mentored new hires, resulting in stronger staff development and increased productivity.
- Scheduled and taught in class and online courses to increase learning opportunities.

Reference Trung Nguyen Trainer 404-275-2084 nguyent510@gmail.com

2013-11 - 2016-11

Area Manager - Talent Acquisition

United States Navy, NRD Seattle, Seattle, WA

- Managed four Navy recruiting stations for enlisted recruiting to include 120 delayed entry program Future Sailors. Developed staff capacity to mentor young adults for entry into the United States Navy Basic Training Program.
- Reference
- Trung Nguyen
- 404-275-2084
- nguyent510@gmail.com

Software

.NET

C#

Visual Studio

SQL

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap 5

Skills

Leadership

Administration

Interpersonal Communication

Planning and Coordination

Organization and Time Management

References

Ron Flaherty

Teacher, San Diego Unified School District 858-472-0233 rflaherty@sandi.net

Tony Velarde

Teacher 951-449-0237 velarde.anthony.nsi@navyjrotc.us

Trung Nguyen

Trainer 404-275-2084 nguyent510@gmail.com